

SKILLS

Data Structures and Algorithms

Git & Github

MySQL - Firebase - SQLite

Bloc Pattern - Riverpod - OOP

Linux

Programming Languages (Java - Java Spring - Dart - Flutter -PHP)

Restful API

LANGUAGES

English (B1 - Intermediate)

Phone Number

+90 552 404 7015

E-posta

enesodabas5234@gmail.com

LinkedIn

www.linkedin.com/in/enessodbs

Address

Adnan Kahveci Caddesi Sülün Sokak No: 3/3 Çekmeköy/İSTANBUL

Github

https://github.com/enessodbs

Website

https://enessodbs.github.io/

ENES ODABAŞ

MOBIL APP DEVELOPER

ABOUT ME

As a Computer Programming graduate and Flutter developer, I have specialized in mobile application development. I have worked on projects using technologies such as API, Firebase, Hive, and SQLite. I gained experience as a Flutter Volunteer Intern at Remora Technology and enhanced my skills through the TechCareer Flutter Bootcamp. I adopt an innovative problem-solving approach and focus on continuous learning.

PROJECTS

FLUTTER E-COMMERCE APP

Technologies and architectures I used in the e-commerce application I developed for the TechCareer Flutter Bootcamp program:

- Bloc Pattern: Utilized Bloc Pattern as the application architecture to reduce code complexity and create a sustainable structure by separating UI/UX from business logic.
- Dio: Processed data retrieved from the API and integrated it into the Flutter application.
- Firebase Authentication: Enabled user registration and login, providing personalized experiences.
- Firestore: Stored user account information and dynamically reflected user data within the application.

CHAT APP

In this project, users logged in with Firebase Authentication can message other users, report messages, block/unblock users, and choose between light and dark theme modes. Technologies and architectures I used:

- Firebase Authentication: Managed user registration and login processes, providing personalized experiences.
- Firestore: Stored user account information and dynamically reflected user data in the application. Additionally, realtime messaging operations were handled through the Firestore database.
- Provider: Simplified state management and made it more convenient using the Provider package.

TODO APP

In this project, I enabled users to easily save both their notes and todos. $\ \ \,$

Technologies and architectures I used:

- Hive: Allowed users to store their todos and notes in the local storage using Flutter's Hive database.
- Bloc Pattern: Used Bloc Pattern as the application architecture to enhance code maintainability and separate business logic from the UI.



SKILLS

Data Structures and Algorithms

Git & Github

MySQL - Firebase - SQLite

Bloc Pattern - Riverpod - OOP

Linux

Programming Languages (Java - Java Spring - Dart - Flutter -PHP)

Restful API

LANGUAGES

English (B1 - Intermediate)

Phone Number

+90 552 404 7015

E-posta

enesodabas5234@gmail.com

LinkedIn

www.linkedin.com/in/enessodbs

Address

Adnan Kahveci Caddesi Sülün Sokak No: 3/3 Çekmeköy/İSTANBUL

Github

https://github.com/enessodbs

Website

https://enessodbs.github.io/

EDUCATION

2022- 2024 **ISTANBUL GEDIK UNIVERSITY**

Computer Programming

2015 - 2019 SABİHA GÖKÇEN ATML

Electrical - Electronic

CERTIFICATES

2024 Flutter Wave Rapid App Development Bootcamp
2024 Mobile Application with Google Flutter
2024 Complete Java Developer Course from Scratch

2024 Version Controls: Git and GitHub

WORK EXPERIENCE

2018-2019 **NETA ELEKTRONÍK A.Ş.**

Quality Control Intern

2024-2024 REMORA TECHNOLOGY

Software Intern

2024-2024 **ISTANBUL GEDIK UNIVERSITY**

IT Support Intern

REFERENCE

Kasım Adalan

Android - IOS Developer & Trainer Telefon : 05372742806